Good morning those welcome to SPI
securities morning podcast. Indian
equity benchmark indices ended
marginally low lower on Tuesday with the
nifty closing below the 25,750
mark amid weekly FNO expiry related
volatility.
Sentiment was also weighed down by
renewed geopolitical concerns after US
President Donald Trump announced a 25%
tariff on countries trading with Iran
raising potential risk for India's
export and static projects such as the
Javar port. FI NL500 K stocks sell key
gas market my DII net bought stocks
worth rupees 1182 in the gas market
yesterday
US stock
red led by a drop in financial share as
comments from JP Morgan executive added
to worries about the US President Donald
Trump's recent proposal for cap on
credit cash rates DJIA said 0.8% 8%
while S&P 500 closed 0.2% lower. Asian
markets posted a modest gain at the
opening today morning in early trade
while Japanese equities extended their
record-breaking run fueled by a weaker
yen
key results announced. Infosys, HDFCMC,
ICIA Prudential EMC, Union Bank, Grow,
Anandati Share and Stock Broker, HDB
Financial Services and Indian Overseas
Bank. Third quarter FI26 results
announced
key results announced post market strong
results from Raa Productivity Enhancer,
Oriental Hotels and Tata Alexi. Decent
set of results from Jes and ICIC lumbar
general insurance
stocks in focus interact building
solutions focus
company has received 130 K rupees order
from a customer to manufacture a
pre-engineer steel building system your
positive medium
next up is NLC India the company has
signed a MOU with the Gujarat government
for the development of large renewable
energy projects in the state project
include
solar, wind, hybrid and battery energy
storage projects this investment
potential at 25,000 K rupees positive in
the medium-term for NCL India
company thomas India's focus company
to boost and promote Gujarat's domestic
tourism positive thomas India in the
medium term saga cement will be in focus
today the company has sell 7.8% 8% stake
of Andra cements via OFS neutral in
short-term for Saga cement. Next up is
Anandatri S and Stock Brokers. I'm
Anandi International Ventures to enter
investment merchant banking business in
gift city. The arm is to carry company's
investment advisory business in the gift
city. Positive in the medium-term for
the company. Next up is Happy Forging.
The company has executed a long-term
land lease pack for solar power plant
project. This is positive in the
medium-term for happy forging. Corporate
action today is the X stock split date
for Kotak Mahindra Bank. The stock will
split from a face value of five to one
per share and a reality the stock will
split from a face value of rupees 10 to
rupees two per share. Shares to exit
anchor lock in Park Med world 2% of
equity will exit share lock in and nefro
care health services 3% of the equity
will exit share lock in today. That's it
for today. Thank you for tuning in.
Investment in securities market are
subject to market risks. Read all the
related documents carefully before
investing.